const questionsDatabase=[
    {
        category:"Geography",
        questions:[
            {
                question:"How many continents are there?",
                answer1:"1",
                answer2:"7",
                answer3:"8",
                answer4:"9",
                answer:"7"
            },
            {
                question:"How many countries end in -stan?",
                answer1:"7",
                answer2:"6",
                answer3:"5",
                answer4:"4",
                answer:"7"
            },
            {
                question:"What continent has the most land area?",
                answer1:"South America",
                answer2:"Asia",
                answer3:"North America",
                answer4:"Africa",
                answer:"Asia"
            },
            {
                question:"Which continent has the biggest population?",
                answer1:"Africa",
                answer2:"Asia",
                answer3:"Europe",
                answer4:"Oceania",
                answer:"Asia"
            },
            {
                question:"What country has the most natural lakes?",
                answer1:"USA",
                answer2:"Finland",
                answer3:"Russia",
                answer4:"Canada",
                answer:"Canada"
            },
            {
                question:"What Country does the Rhine River run through?",
                answer1:"Scotland",
                answer2:"France",
                answer3:"Germany",
                answer4:"Hungary",
                answer:"Germany"
            },
            {
                question:"What is the name of the deepest lake in the world?",
                answer1:"Lake Baikal",
                answer2:"Capsian Sea",
                answer3:"The Great Slave Lake",
                answer4:"Lake Huron",
                answer:"Lake Baikal"
            },
            {
                question:"What is the name of the biggest lake in the world?",
                answer1:"Lake Superior",
                answer2:"Black Sea",
                answer3:"Caspian Sea",
                answer4:"Lake Victoria",
                answer:"Caspian Sea"
            },
            {
                question:"Which ocean is the deepest?",
                answer1:"Southern (Antartic)",
                answer2:"Pacific",
                answer3:"Atlantic",
                answer4:"Artic",
                answer:"Pacific"
            },
            {
                question:"Which ocean is the largest?",
                answer1:"Pacific",
                answer2:"Indian",
                answer3:"Atlantic",
                answer4:"Artic",
                answer:"Pacific"
            }
            
            
        ]
        
    },
    {
        category:"Sack",
        questions:[
            {
                question:"Which animal does Jack like most?",
                answer1:"Whitetail deer",
                answer2:"Flying snake",
                answer3:"Megladon",
                answer4:"Flying squirrel",
                answer:"Whitetail deer"
            },
            {
                question:"What is Sydney's least favorite word",
                answer1:"Pickle",
                answer2:"Boombox",
                answer3:"Trampoline",
                answer4:"Mushroom",
                answer:"Boombox",

            },
            {
                question:"Has Sydney ever gone ziplining?",
                answer1:"yes",
                answer2: "no",
                answer: "yes"
            },
            {
                question:"Does Sydney want to go skydiving at some point?",
                answer1:"yes",
                answer2:"no",
                answer:"yes"
            },
            {
                question:"What is Sydney's sign?",
                answer1:"Pisces",
                answer2:"Sagittarius",
                answer3:"Virgo",
                answer4:"Scorpio",
                answer:"Scorpio"
            },
            {
                question:"What is Sydney's moon sign",
                answer1:"Aries",
                answer2:"Sagittarius",
                answer3:"Libra",
                answer4:"Scorpio",
                answer:"Aries"
            }
        ]
        
    },
    {
        category:"Drexel",
        questions:[
            {   
                question:"Where is Drexel located?",
                answer1:"Philadelphia",
                answer2:"New York",
                answer3:"Pittsburg",
                answer4:"Scranton",
                answer:"Philadelphia"
            },
            {
                question:"What is the tallest building in Philly?",
                answer1:"Two Liberty Place",
                answer2:"The Empire State Building",
                answer3:"Comcast Technology Center",
                answer4:"1250 Market Street",
                answer:"Comcast Technology Center"
            }
        ]
        
    },
    {
        category:"Trivia",
        questions:[
            {
                question:"What was the first youtube channel to get 100 million subscribers?",
                answer1:"T-series",
                answer2:"JustinBeiber",
                answer3:"Jacksepticeye",
                answer4:"Pewdiepie",
                answer:"T-series"
            },
            {
                question:"Who was the winner of the 2021-2022 superbowl?",
                answer1:"Texans",
                answer2:"Patriots",
                answer3:"Bengals",
                answer4:"Rams",
                answer:"Rams"
            },
            {
                question:"How many trains does the MTA have excluding shuttles?",
                answer1:"25",
                answer2:"28",
                answer3:"21",
                answer4:"19",
                answer:"25"
            }
        ]

    }
]


// Structure woulda been better if I had just had an object with the categories as objects within it that way it could be named.
// But maybe not because IDK how to add fields to an object programatically
const emojisDatabase={
    goodEmojis:[
        '👌','😍','👍','💯','✅','🤑','😎','🤩','😁','💪','🔥','👑','💰','💸','⭐','✨','🌟','🥇','🏆','🍰','💐','🍦','🌹'
    ],
    badEmojis:[
        '🤨','🙃','😨','😡','🤬','🥶','🤢','🤮','☠️','👎','🦽','🚽','💩','💔','❌','🚫'
    ]
}